

# Cris Zhou

E-mail: meixi@live.cn Phone: 15721279956

Website: https://github.com/orgs/Baluoteli/dashbo

Address: Hangzhou Cixi first officer park

Experienced in the streaming media application industry. I have extensive experience in both streaming media servers and recording. In addition, I also have a lot of development experience in application development, especially in the education and entertainment industry. There is also a lot of open source maintenance experience such as vlc, obs, ffmpeg, etc..

## Work experience

#### Alibaba Cainiao Smart Logistics Network Limited

C++ Senior Software Engineer

Development and maintenance of warehouse terminal equipment, user interface product with qt; audio/video business

Sep 2019 — Present

#### Agora.io

C++ Senior Software Engineer

Development of streaming media-related education and entertainment applications SDK about Audio/video. Hook Audio on mainly music player; wrapper on obs. Windows device driver about audio/video capture codec.

Oct 2017 — Nov 2019

#### Shanghai Able Digital & Tech Co., Ltd

C++ Senior Software Engineer

The able electronics business is online mooc education. my work in mainly three part: media video server ,media recording ,director; also need to develop many application tools

### Education

## Computer Science and technology

Hubei Institute of technology

Computer Science and technology 1

Nov 2014 — Oct 2017

Jan 2010 — Jan 2014